* Features

* Features

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to BannerNow, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to BannerNow, Inc. include BannerNow. BannerNow is an online platform for producing and serving animated ads. This policy describes details about privacy on Bannernow website, and ads produced by Bannernow platform, as well as details about compliance with [GDPR](https://gdpr-info.eu/). By using BannerNow, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

As part of its commitment to consumer privacy, Bannernow has implemented and follows the specifications and policies of the IAB EU Transparency & Consent Framework (TCF) as part of our compliance with EU data protection law. See [https://iabeurope.eu/tcf-2-0/](https://iabeurope.eu/tcf-2-0/) for more information. Bannernow’s vendor identification number within the TCF is **801**.

Collection of your Personal Information (website)
-------------------------------------------------

BannerNow may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by BannerNow. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the BannerNow website. BannerNow encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from BannerNow so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. BannerNow is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the BannerNow website.

Collection of your Personal Information (BannerNow AdServer)
------------------------------------------------------------

BannerNow AdServer does not collect any private information via cookies or otherwise. Bannernow AdServer collects some analytics information related to the ads produced on Bannernow platform. This analytics information includes countries from which ads are viewed, number of impressions and clicks, and domains on which ads are served.

Use of your Personal Information (website)
------------------------------------------

BannerNow collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. BannerNow may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from BannerNow and its affiliates. BannerNow may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. BannerNow does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. BannerNow may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to BannerNow, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. BannerNow may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within BannerNow, in order to determine what BannerNow services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within BannerNow to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. BannerNow will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BannerNow or the site;
* protect and defend the rights or property of BannerNow; and,
* act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BannerNow, or the public.

Use of your Personal Information (Bannernow AdServer)
-----------------------------------------------------

Bannernow AdServer is collecting the IP address automatically as part of an Ad impression request. This information is used generate the reporting Some of the device and usage data collected by the services, whether alone or in conjunction with other data, could be personally identifying to you. Please note that this device and usage data is primarily used to identify the uniqueness of each user logging on (as opposed to specific individuals), apart from where it is strictly required to identify an individual for security purposes or as required as part of our provision of the services to our customers.

* conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BannerNow or the site;
* protect and defend the rights or property of BannerNow; and,
* act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BannerNow, or the public.

Security of your Personal Information (website)
-----------------------------------------------

BannerNow secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. Your credit card information is not stored anywhere on BannerNow. All Credit card information is saved in payment processor's account (PAYPAL or Stripe) in the encoded format so it is fully secure and cannot be accessed even by us.

Your Content in our Platform
----------------------------

BannerNow allows you to upload, store, and publish content. You retain ownership of any intellectual property rights that you hold in that content. When you upload, store, publish send or receive content to or through our services, you give BannerNow (and those we work with) a worldwide license to use, host, store, reproduce, modify, create derivative works (such as those resulting from translations, adaptations or other changes we make so that your content works better with our services), communicate, publish, publicly perform, publicly display and distribute such content. The rights you grant in this license are for the limited purpose of operating, promoting, and improving our Services. This license continues even if you stop using our Services (for example, we might keep serving your ad). Some Services may offer you ways to access and remove content that has been provided to that Service. Also, in some of our Services, there are terms or settings that narrow the scope of our use of the content submitted in those Services. Make sure you have the necessary rights to grant us this license for any content that you submit to our Services. Also you must ensure that your content is malware-free. We reserve a right to suspend any ad that displays any malicious behavior.

Children Under Sixteen
----------------------

BannerNow does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen(16), you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
---------------------

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from BannerNow by contacting us at support @ bannernow.com

You can also opt-out from cookies [here](https://bannernow.com/cookies)

EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION
-------------------------------------

If you are a resident of the European Union ("EU"), United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") with respect to your Personal Data, as outlined below.  
For this section, we use the terms "Personal Data" and "processing" as they are defined in the GDPR, but "Personal Data" generally means information that can be used to individually identify a person, and "processing" generally covers actions that can be performed in connection with data such as collection, use, storage and disclosure. Company will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with the Services.  
Where applicable, this section is intended to supplement, and not replace, this Privacy Policy. If there are any conflicts between this section and any other provision of this Privacy Policy, the policy or portion that is more protective of Personal Data shall control to the extent of such conflict. If you have any questions about this section or whether any of the following applies to you, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://bannernow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

What Personal Data Does BannerNow (website) Collect From You?
-------------------------------------------------------------

BannerNow collects Personal Data about you when you provide such information directly to us or when Personal Data about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our Services.  
**Information BannerNow collects directly from you**  
BannerNow receives Personal Data directly from you when you provide us with such Personal Data, including without limitation the following:

* First and last name
* Email addresses
* Address

**Information we automatically collect when you use BannerNow Services**  
Some Personal Data is automatically collected when you use our Services, such as the following:

* IP address
* Device identifiers (via Google Analytics)
* Web browser information (via Google Analytics)
* Page view statistics (via Google Analytics)
* Browsing history (via Google Analytics)
* Usage information (via Google Analytics)
* Transaction information (e.g. transaction amount, date and time such transaction occurred)
* Cookies and other tracking technologies
* Log data (e.g. access times, hardware and software information)

How Do We Use Your Personal Data?
---------------------------------

We process Personal Data to operate, improve, understand and personalize our Services. For example, we use Personal Data to:

* Create and manage user profiles
* Communicate with you about the Services
* Process orders
* Contact you about Service announcements, updates or offers
* Provide support and assistance for the Services
* Personalize website content and communications based on your preferences
* Meet contract or legal obligations
* Respond to user inquiries
* Fulfill user requests
* Comply with our legal or contractual obligations
* Resolve disputes
* Protect against or deter fraudulent, illegal or harmful actions
* Enforce our Terms of Use

Google AdManager and DV360 integrations
---------------------------------------

Bannernow's use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to Google API Services User Data Policy, including the Limited Use requirements.

How and With Whom Do We Share Your Data (website)?
--------------------------------------------------

We share Personal Data with vendors, third party service providers and agents who work on our behalf and provide us with services related to the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. These parties include:

* Payment processors (Stripe)
* Fraud prevention service providers
* Ad networks and partners
* Analytics service providers
* Hosting service providers

We also share Personal Data when we believe it is necessary to:

* Comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process, including from law enforcement or other government agencies
* Protect us, our business or our users, for example to enforce our Terms of Use, prevent spam or other unwanted communications and investigate or protect against fraud
* Maintain the security of our products and services

We also share information with third parties when you give us consent to do so.

How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Data?
-----------------------------------------

We retain Personal Data about you for as long as you have an open account with us or as otherwise necessary to provide you Services.

What Rights Do You Have Regarding Your Personal Data?
-----------------------------------------------------

You have certain rights with respect to your Personal Data, including those set forth below. For more information about these rights, or to submit a request, please email [\[email protected\]](https://bannernow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note that in some circumstances, we may not be able to fully comply with your request, such as if it is frivolous or extremely impractical, if it jeopardizes the rights of others, or if it is not required by law, but in those circumstances, we will still respond to notify you of such a decision. In some cases, we may also need to you to provide us with additional information, which may include Personal Data, if necessary to verify your identity and the nature of your request.

* Access: You can request more information about the Personal Data we hold about you and request a copy of such Personal Data. You can also access certain of your Personal Data by accessing your account profile.
* Rectification: If you believe that any Personal Data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data. You can also correct some of this information directly by accessing your account profile.
* Erasure: You can request that we erase some or all of your Personal Data from our systems.
* Withdrawal of Consent: If we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that if you exercise this right, you may have to then provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Data, if such use or disclosure is necessary to enable you to utilize some or all of our Services.
* Portability: You can ask for a copy of your Personal Data in a machine-readable format. You can also request that we transmit the data to another controller where technically feasible.
* Objection: You can contact us to let us know that you object to the further use or disclosure of your Personal Data for certain purposes, such as for direct marketing purposes.
* Restriction of Processing: You can ask us to restrict further processing of your Personal Data.
* Right to File Complaint: You have the right to lodge a complaint about Company’s practices with respect to your Personal Data with the supervisory authority of your country or EU Member State.

Transfers of Personal Data
--------------------------

The Services are hosted and operated in the United States ("U.S.") through Company and its service providers, and if you do not reside in the U.S., laws in the U.S. may differ from the laws where you reside. By using the Services, you acknowledge that any Personal Data about you, regardless of whether provided by you or obtained from a third party, is being provided to Company in the U.S. and will be hosted on U.S. servers, and you authorize Company to transfer, store and process your information to and in the U.S., and possibly other countries.

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

BannerNow will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. BannerNow encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how BannerNow is protecting your information.

Contact Information
-------------------

BannerNow welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that BannerNow has not adhere to this Statement, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://bannernow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Effective as of May 24, 2022

#### Banner Maker Tool

#### Features

©2024 BannerNow, Inc. All rights reserved

#### Info

* [\[email protected\]](https://bannernow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

©2024 BannerNow, Inc. All rights reserved
